newsexstory.com 2015-12-27

# Privacy Policy - New Sex Story

At newsexstory.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit newsexstory.com, and how we safeguard your information. We will NEVER sell your personal information to third parties.

If you are asked to provide information when using this website, it will ONLY be used in the ways described in this privacy policy.

This policy is updated from time to time. The latest version is published on this page.

This website privacy policy was updated on: September 30, 2015

If you have any questions about this policy, please [contact us](http://newsexstory.com/contact/).

**Introduction**

We gather and use certain information about individuals in order to provide products and services and to enable certain functions on this website.

We also collect information to better understand how visitors use this website and to present timely, relevant information to them, such as Google Analytics.

**What Data We Gather**

We may collect the following information:

Name and job title  
Contact information including email address  
Demographic information, such as postcode, preferences and interests  
Website usage data  
Other information relevant to client enquiries  
Other information pertaining to special offers and surveys  
How We Use This Data

Collecting this data helps us understand what you are looking from the company, enabling us to deliver improved products and services.

Specifically, we may use data:

For our own internal records  
To improve the products and services we provide  
To contact you in response to a specific enquiry  
To customise the website for you  
To send you promotional emails about products, services, offers and other things we think might be relevant to you.  
To send you promotional mailings or to call you about products, services, offers and other things we think might be relevant to you.  
To contact you via email, telephone or mail for market research reasons.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on newsexstory.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick DART Cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

**Controlling Cookies**

You can use your web browser’s cookie settings to determine how our website uses cookies. If you do not want our website to store cookies on your computer or device, you should set your web browser to refuse cookies.

However, please note that doing this may affect how our website functions. Some pages and services may become unavailable to you.

Unless you have changed your browser to refuse cookies, our website will issue cookies when you visit it.

**Controlling Information about You**

When you fill in a form or provide your details on our website, you will see one or more tick boxes allowing you to:

  * Opt-in to receive marketing communications from us by email, telephone, text message or post.
  * Opt-in to receive marketing communications from our third-party partners by email, telephone, text message or post.
  * If you have agreed that we can use your information for marketing purposes, you can change your mind easily, via one of these methods: 1. Sign in to our website and change your opt-in settings, 2. [Contacting us](http://newsexstory.com/contact/).

We will never lease, distribute or sell your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or the law requires us to.

Any personal information we hold about you is stored and processed under our data protection policy, in line with the Data Protection Act 1998.

**Security**

We will always hold your information securely.

To prevent unauthorized disclosure or access to your information, we have implemented strong physical and electronic security safeguards.

We also follow stringent procedures to ensure we work with all personal data in line with the Data Protection Act 1998.

**Links from Our Site**

Our website may contain links to other websites.

Please note that we have no control of websites outside the newsexstory.com domain. If you provide information to a website to which we link, we are not responsible for its protection and privacy.

Always be wary when submitting data to websites. Read the site’s data protection and privacy policies fully.
